Alice Granger

123 My Road, San Diego, CA 93847 a.granger@myemail.com (746) 729-1038

Seasoned senior front desk medical receptionist with 10+ years of experience providing outstanding administrative support in major San Diego hospitals. Superb organizational ability with a proven track record for punctual and attentive patient service. Inspiring and motivational leader with a keen aptitude for performance management and colleague training.

Key Skills

- Leadership and mentoring
- Strong organizational skills
- · Microsoft Office Suite
- Scheduling and appointment management
- Customer service
- Telephone and email

Professional Experience

Senior Medical Front Desk Receptionist

Rady Children's Hospital of San Diego, San Diego, CA j September 2015 - Present

- Coordinate the appointment booking and professional meeting schedule, introducing changes that reduced wastage by 84% since 2017
- Maintain precise and updated patient records, performing regular reviews to increase accuracy by 98% over three years
- Oversee a team of 5 administrative staff and undertake regular performance reviewsand professional development activities
- Train and onboard new colleagues to improve their understanding of administrative processes and patient service skills

Medical Receptionist

UC San Diego, San Diego, CA | July 2010- September 2015

- Answered telephone and email queries politely and efficiently and redirected communications to the correct departments
- Provided sensitive and effective support to patients, maintaining a 99.5%+ satisfaction rating throughout employment
- Coordinated the billing process and generated invoices with 100% accuracy over 5 years
- Performed regular stock takes of office supplies and ordered replenishments

Education

Associate of Science in Healthcare Administration
PIMA Medical Institute, Chula Vista, CA September 2008 - June 2010